

Eden Coania

B.Sc Applied mathematician

started my degree while on high school in applied math. served 6 years in Israel Navy Underwater System Warefare Branch as project and product manager and interacting with security industries at Israel and abroad. self-learning fullstack.

edencoania@gmail.com

0525258159

rishon lezion

in linkedin.com/in/eden-coania-9377a0a2

github.com/edencoani

WORK EXPERIENCE

Anti Submarine Warfare - Sonar Project manager Israel navy

11/2021 - 11/2022

LT CMD

- A large scale project, with management focus, and high budget(13M\$).
- Leading contract reviews and ICD'S from client side.
- Military equipment and technology development.
- Testing and evaluation of military products
- Managing operational and technician courses in IN facilities.
- Executing highly complicated installation in short time.

Submarine development - project manager Israel navy

03/2017 - 11/2021

Achievements/Tasks

- Head sector for a year managing 5 engineers officers.
- Product strategy and roadmap development.
- · Managing wide range of projects to support the flotilla, from projects in the finish line until new ideas to problems that needed the solution next week.
- Client project managing with abroad security companies.
- Played a key role in the management of computer systems, including software and hardware upgrades, maintenance, and troubleshooting.
- Leading high complexity experiments.
- Cross-functional team leadership and collaboration.
- Assist and analysis complex engineering malfunctions.

EDUCATION

B.Sc Applied mathematician

Bar Ilan University

07/2014 - 07/2018

Courses in coding

• Intro to programing - in c.

Object Oriented Programing -

fullstack self learning

01/2023 - Present

topics • HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Node js

React

SKILLS

JavaScript

PERSONAL PROJECTS

website - group and eventing.

- Creating a website with the purpose of making groups and making events.
- Main capabilities including adding friends, creating groups, joining existing groups, creating events, inviting to events and RSVP.
- Making user interface, lives along with the server in React.
- The project contain fully login/signup process include Tokens to connect, and working with JSONs in nodeJS.
- front hosted in GitHub Pages, server hosted in Render.
- https://edencoania.github.io/

LANGUAGES

Hebrew

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Spanish

Elementary Proficiency

INTERESTS

Soccer

Volleyball

Game-theory